<resources>
    <string name="app_name">GoalSetterDemo</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="dummy_text">
        Bacon ipsum dolor amet short ribs filet mignon tri-tip, beef sausage cupim ground round
        turkey. Flank strip steak tenderloin cupim, short loin brisket ham hock. Kielbasa drumstick
        rump, sausage cow ground round tenderloin jowl ham hock doner ribeye cupim pork belly spare
        ribs. Rump short loin landjaeger, meatloaf ball tip shoulder jerky turducken. Ground round
        pork loin doner, t-bone sausage shank turducken tri-tip pancetta filet mignon brisket cupim
        bresaola landjaeger. Andouille chicken landjaeger doner, corned beef pork cow pork belly short
        ribs fatback meatball cupim strip steak shankle. Chuck shankle landjaeger pig shank
        andouille porchetta, kevin venison shoulder tri-tip boudin bresaola beef.

        Frankfurter filet mignon cow flank. Sausage porchetta kevin cupim, pork chop meatloaf doner
        alcatra corned beef ham hock turkey. Venison beef ribs rump boudin ball tip spare ribs.
        Turkey jowl leberkas chuck tail. Shank swine pastrami pork chop ham hock pork bresaola turkey
        brisket cupim spare ribs meatloaf salami turducken. Ham hock kielbasa meatloaf, bresaola
        tenderloin alcatra hamburger landjaeger shank. Salami chicken corned beef, porchetta strip
        steak sausage doner bresaola tail fatback tenderloin.

        Fatback chicken short ribs meatball turducken doner. Corned beef jerky doner turducken,
        venison pork fatback. Sirloin shoulder porchetta landjaeger ball tip biltong capicola turkey
        pig meatloaf tri-tip beef ribs filet mignon. Chuck short loin tongue, pork chop meatball shank jerky.

        Frankfurter doner turkey beef ribs rump flank. Swine pancetta beef ribs, bresaola pork
        landjaeger corned beef ham hock beef pork chop tenderloin jowl short loin tri-tip. Beef
        ribs spare ribs doner, pork chop chuck shankle pork loin kielbasa. Biltong beef sirloin
        meatball boudin hamburger. Hamburger kielbasa doner, rump tenderloin sausage short ribs.
        Capicola sausage biltong chicken. Ball tip ham landjaeger brisket shank shankle.

        Biltong ribeye beef porchetta flank capicola pork chop fatback rump picanha bresaola.
        Landjaeger rump sirloin, frankfurter shankle ham hock tongue biltong pancetta leberkas
        capicola beef t-bone ball tip jerky. Drumstick biltong prosciutto, meatball jowl spare
        ribs bresaola alcatra beef ribs sirloin. Hamburger boudin ham hock ham, doner t-bone chuck
        pork belly pastrami tail leberkas sausage shoulder picanha swine. Shankle pork belly ball
        tip hamburger turkey filet mignon corned beef tenderloin spare ribs. Pork loin flank pork,
        ribeye tail short loin alcatra filet mignon sausage bresaola. Chicken ribeye turkey brisket,
        pork frankfurter capicola jerky.
    </string>
</resources>
